teensglamour.com 2018-05-15

# 

* * *

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact teensglamour.com via the contact information provided at page end.

## Information Collection

teensglamour.com is the sole owner of the information collected from the website.

## Profile

We store information that we collect via browser cookies, log files, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we maintain for individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and to improve the content of the web site for the user. This profile is used to tailor users' visits to our web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share user profiles with third parties.

## Browser Cookies

A browser cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file instructions. Advertising cookies may be placed to enable our display advertising partner to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with our website. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. 

## Third-Party Advertising

teensglamour.com is not responsible for third-party advertising on its web site.

## Log Files

Like most standard web site servers, we maintain log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad, aggregate demographic information.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or a legal process served on our web site.

## Security

teensglamour.com takes every precaution to protect our client's information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both on- and off- line.

All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted within our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job, for example, our customer service representatives, are granted access to personally identifiable information.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## Makeup for Brown Eyes

Even though brown eyes are the most common color we have to admit that if you have brown eyes you can experiment in so many different ways. We don’t think that you cannot do it with green, blue or other colors, but it somehow seems easier to experiment with brown eyes than with other colors.…

## Detox Tea Comes To The Aid Of Those Looking For A Healthy, Glowing Skin Without Any Blemishes

For those looking for a glowing skin, they are advised to head for a detoxification of the skin. The body accumulates a lot of toxins in the normal course of our lives from junk food and other sources. A detox is the only way to get rid of all these. If you want your skin to glow like it was born…

## Discover The Secrets Of Olive-Oil When You Try It On For Your Skin And Nails

Olive-oil is known to be a very good accompanist when you are out cooking your favorite dish. But there are a large number of positive effects of the application of olive-oil to your skin. Olive-oil was a part of the beauty secrets maintained by Queen Cleopatra, but with the discoveries made in the…

## Use An Eyebrow-Brush And Hair-Oil Properly To Foster Good And Proper Growth Of Eyebrows

You can also stimulate hair growth on your eyebrows by using an eyebrow brush in the proper manner. Always use the brush in the direction in which the hair grows. This way, you are going to avoid any chances of hair damage. A mere two-minute application of the eyebrow brush can do the trick for you.…

## The Eyebrows Certainly Add To The Values Of Beauty

The perfect eyebrows of the protagonist on the silver screen are certainly very attractive. The pencil thin and naturally shaped eyebrows offer a distinct impact of the beauty of the person on the screen. And the best thing about eyebrows is that, unlike all other features, the pencil-thin eyebrows…

Copyright © 2018 . All Rights Reserved.
